<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HOME PAGE  on Building Ideas</title>
    <link>http://simona.com.np/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HOME PAGE  on Building Ideas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:39:58 +0545</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://simona.com.np/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Authoritative Vs Non-Authoritative </title>
      <link>http://simona.com.np/dns/authoritative/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:39:58 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://simona.com.np/dns/authoritative/</guid>
      <description>What is Non-Authoritative DNS ?
Simply stating non-authoritative DNS does not contain the original files of the namespace zone. They usually have cache for that particular domain which is usually generated from previous iterative query done towards Root, TLD and then to the authoritative nameserver .If a DNS server responded for a DNS query which doesn’t have its original file information it is known as a Non-authoritative answer.
Let&amp;rsquo;s have a look at a simple packet capture to help it understand better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cisco-R1# reload in/at  A Life Saver ! </title>
      <link>http://simona.com.np/cisco/reload/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:39:58 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://simona.com.np/cisco/reload/</guid>
      <description>We are well aware of how tricky can our life get when we are making some changes into our network device configuration and suddenly the ssh access gets disconnected , which can be more interesting if the device is in the Data Centre . We will either need to reboot the device physically going to the location to gain our old configuration or be very precise by using this life saver command in Cisco devices which I will be discussing about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSPF Adjacency State </title>
      <link>http://simona.com.np/cisco/ospf-adjacency-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:39:58 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://simona.com.np/cisco/ospf-adjacency-state/</guid>
      <description>OSPF has always been one of the most difficult dynamic routing protocols personally for me to understand if we try to deep dive into the protocol itself. In this blog let me briefly explain the different adjacency state that 2 routers go through before they exchange the route.
  Down
 No hello has been received from the neighbors.    Attempt
 Unicast hello has been sent to the neighbor router but no hello has been received back yet    Init</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNAT and Auto Map</title>
      <link>http://simona.com.np/big-ip-f5/snat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:39:58 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://simona.com.np/big-ip-f5/snat/</guid>
      <description>This is going to be my first blog in the technology that I am starting to love pretty much. Yes, as my topic suggests we are going to talk about an technology which all the time used to come in my mind as a loadbalancer but finally I started stating it as a Application Delivery Controller which it really is . Big IP F5 has become one of the hot topics over the years that provides intelligent traffic management, high availability of your critical applications, security, optimization and many more things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Chassis </title>
      <link>http://simona.com.np/junipe/vc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 20:39:58 +0545</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://simona.com.np/junipe/vc/</guid>
      <description>Juniper has always been an technology that I have always liked right from the beginning of my career when I was working as an Jr Network Administrator. The logical command as well as the hierarchy based Juniper devices has always made me love the device.
Let me today talk about a very useful and an interesting topic which we usually called stack in the world of Cisco and virtual chassis in the world of Juniper, both of them mean the same thing logically make two or more than two switch as a one and configure and manage the device as a single unity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>